Favour Agozie

07031035401

(7) f-gozie

in Agozie Favour

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Bilingual software developer with a customer driven nature and a focus on working as part of a team. Excellent communicator with the ability to meet deadlines and quickly resolve issues. Multi-faceted software developer knowledgeable in Python, Java and C#. True team player offering 4+ years of experience in the industry.

SKILLS

Python
Proficient
Intermediate
HTML/CSS
Javascript
Intermediate
Intermediate
ReactJS/ React Native
Novice
Proficient

CERTIFICATIONS

Introduction to User Experience Design

Coursera

Credential ID: RZHR4LPJBDTJ

Leading transformations: Manage change

Coursera

Credential ID: U8QR47CP2ZRC

Artificial Intelligence Analyst -Mastery Award 2019

IBM

Credential ID: 3663-1581-7933-0130

LANGUAGES

English

Igbo

Native Elementary

WORK EXPERIENCE

SaVests

Software Developer Intern

(September 2020 - Present)

I wrote clean code to develop functional web and mobile applications. I also helped to troubleshoot and debug applications, as well as wrote tests to optimize performance. I also collaborated with frontend developers to integrate user-facing elements with server side logic. I provided training and support to non-technical teams and also built reusable code and libraries to ease subsequent development processes.

GitIT Technologies Limited

Software Developer Intern

(February 2019 - August 2020)

I wrote Python scripts to automate already existing manual processes. Refactored Python scripts and converted them to their Java alternatives to better fit the stack. I also developed and implemented a skin color transfer program as well as setup and maintained the Linux servers on which our programs ran.

National Identity Management Commission

(December 2018 - July 2019)

Software Developer Intern

I designed and developed optimized apis for capturing identity records on other platforms. I also worked in collaboration with other developers in debugging already existing applications as well as implemented new features and troubleshot database related issues.

National Gas Company

Industrial Trainee

(May 2017 - August 2017)

I installed and managed their servers, as well as training and providing support to other nontech members to properly use company required software.

EDUCATION

Covenant University

Bachelor's Degree Computer Science

(August 2016 - January 2021)

PROJECTS

Fifton Academy

https://www.fiftonacademy.com

November 2019

Designed and developed both the frontend and backend using Django and HTML/CSS with JavaScript

Skin Color Transfer

https://github.com/f-gozie/skin-color-transfer

Designed and developed using Python and OpenCV

Computer Vision

https://github.com/f-gozie/computer-vision

February 2019

June 2020

Designed and developed using Python and OpenCV